

Master of Business Economics, extensive Data analytics, SAP Application Support & Business Intelligence experience in Financial Services, Retail and Banking industries focusing on Accounting, Forecasting, Risk, CRM and Marketing. Apart from possessing very strong technical skills, Zita is a great team player to work with.

## **QAULIFICATION**

# Banking & Corp. Financial Analysis

- Hierarchical Master Data Management
- ♦ Financial modeling on budget, forecasting
- ♦ Revenue & Gross Margin, what-if analysis
- Reconciliation and variance analysis

# CRM, Marketing & Campaign

- Customer Transaction Analyses
- ♦ Customer RFM Model
- Campaign before and after analyses
- Market Share & Strategic Selection

#### Data Centric

- End-to-end data analysis with insights
- Data modeling, cleansing, transformation
- Data visualization, Dashboard
- Data Quality, MDM, Data flow chart

#### Technical Skills

- ♦ Application Implementation: SAP, Process Flow
- Data: Advanced SQL, SQL Server, Access, Python
- Dashboard: Excel, Tableau, Power BI, Google Analytics
- ♦ Others: Jira, ServiceNow, Draw.io

### **EDUCATION**

- Master of Arts in Business Economics | GPA: A+| Wilfrid Laurier University | Sep 2020 Jun 2022
- Honors Bachelor of Arts in Economics | Wilfrid Laurier University | Sep 2016 May 2020
- Certificate | Google Analytics 2022 | SQL for Data Analysis Udcity 2022

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE - INTERN**

## Wealth Management Analyst | Jining MengShang Rural Bank

Mar 2022 – Aug 2022

- Banking Customer Transaction Analyses Conducted retail banking CRM analysis by utilizing RFM model,
   transaction and category analysis to provide key insights for redefining campaign implementation strategy
- Delivered risk analysis to identify suspicious & problematic transactions base on business rules through data modeling, integration and reporting with combining and linking data from various sources
- Developed solid understanding in bank lending products, credit risk measurements & credit adjudication process
- Effectively adjudicated a daily pipeline of 50 loans to maintain service level agreements with internal stakeholders
- Credit Risk Analysis using Logistic Regression in R to reduce the Bad Loan Error Rate for loan application
- Performed reconciliation in operational data & reports to wrap up and ensure the accuracy of branch reporting
- Collated and analyzed the data of insurance, funds and closed-end wealth management products, producing 66
  daily sales reports and 12 weekly reports of wealth management products by using Excel

# **Analyst Consultant | Inossem Canada Inc.**

May 2021 – Jan 2022

- Participated in SAP implementation for Segway Inc. and Powersports Canada as a Finance & Cost consultant;
- Gathered requirements; summarized pain points, and provided solutions with best-practices
- Cooperated with consultants from other modules such as SAP SD and MM on system integration testing
- identifying potential issues in business processes and discovering opportunities of system improvements
- Conducted Master Data Cleansing and standardization; configured enterprise level Product Hierarchy
- Managed multi-parties' communication and organized weekly meetings with customers to review CRs, incidents, and ad hock requests based on business logic & operational workflow

# Business Analyst | ZheShang Fund Management Co., Ltd

May 2019 - Sep 2019

- Maintained customer profile database to ensure client information accuracy and status up to date
- Analyzed campaign performance by region, product, and time through trending, variance analysis
- Prepared monthly investor performance report by products and investment categories
- Categorized customer groups on identifying potential targets; assessed churn risks through what-if analysis

#### Data Analyst | Oppein Home Group

May 2017 - Sep 2017

- Coordinated with department of marketing, operations and finance to improve process efficiency
- Created and maintained 3-year sales forecasts and financial outlook reports
- Prepared sales and marketing KPI reports (average revenue per customer, sales funnel performance, impression, leads, and conversion rate)